You have a ligament that can almost be considered
ほとんど
a kind of small diaphragm
小さな横隔膜
which is called the membrane of the illiquist.
と見なせる靭帯があります。それは「不確実膜」と呼ばれます。
It attaches, it inserts at the level of the
それは第三脳室のレベルに付着し、
third ventricle
第三脳室のレベルに挿入され、
and descends to the level of the sphenoid spray.
蝶形骨のスプレーのレベルまで下降します。
And within that, you have an important passage.
そしてその中には、重要な通路があります。
with the oculomotor nerve, you see,
動眼神経と一緒に、分かりますか？
and all the arterial passage here with the basilar trunk
そして、ここに脳底動脈幹を持つすべての動脈通路があり、
to form the cerebral arteries, etc.,
脳動脈などを形成するために、
which position themselves here, you see.
ここに配置されます、分かりますか？
This is sphenoid.
これは蝶形骨です。
And so, when this descends, it creates an axis of tension
したがって、これが下降すると、緊張の軸と
and a movement that occurs on the ventricular system.
脳室系で起こる動きが生まれます。
This is my third ventricle.
これは私の第三脳室です。
Fourth ventricle.
第四脳室。
which will be like this,
このように、
fourth ventricle,
第四脳室、
and then the tooth,
そして歯、
Monro's foramen,
モンロー孔、
and my lateral ventricles.
そして私の側脳室。
You see?
分かりますか？
Here, I have a small
ここに小さな
kind of tension pattern
緊張のパターンがあり、
that sets in,
それが生じ、
and which has a whole action
そしてそれは全体的な作用を持っています。
on the space
下垂体が配置される
where the pituitary gland is located.
空間に。
And what comes
そして、何が
above the pituitary gland?
下垂体の上に来るのでしょうか？
You have another tissue,
別の組織があります。
you have the optic chiasm,
視交叉があります。
around 30 degrees
約30度で、
with a movement
5度の動きが
of 5 degrees possible.
可能です。
And this movement
そしてこの動きは、
creates a whole drainage space
私の第三脳室と
in fact very important
私の蝶形骨の間に、
between my third ventricle,
実際には非常に重要な
my sphenoid,
排水空間全体を作り出します。
and these micro-vessels that are there.
そしてそこにあるこれらの微小血管。
I also have what are called pericytes.
また、周皮細胞と呼ばれるものもあります。
Pericytes,
周皮細胞は、
they are in the micro-capillaries
微小毛細血管の中にあり、
and their relationship with the nerves.
神経との関係があります。
of the blood-brain barrier spaces,
血液脳関門の空間、
it's a fulcrum, it's a big deep fulcrum.
それは支点であり、大きな支持点です。
When you take
深い。あなたが
your presphenoids,
あなたの前蝶形骨を
you see, here, your presphenoids,
ほら、ここに、あなたの前蝶形骨、
you are your occiput, you are between the two,
あなたは後頭骨、あなたは両者の間にいる、
this space
この空間
where you balance
あなたが揺れる
on the membrane of the illiquist.
液体の膜の上で。
We see it here, you see,
ここに見えますね、ほら、
membrane of, here,
膜の、ここに、
with this third ventricle,
この第三脳室とともに、
we see here, you see, all this
ここに見えますね、このすべての
membranous tension that deals
膜の張力が
with the nerve and also passes through the vessels and very close to my
神経を占め、血管の中も通り、私の
pituitary gland, that's where I have
下垂体のすぐ近くにあり、そこに
all this balance point where my whole nervous system will communicate with
私の神経系全体が
my hormonal system
私のホルモン系とコミュニケーションをとる、このバランスのポイント全体があります。
the hypothalamo-pituitary-thyroid-adrenal-gonadal axis
視床下部-下垂体-甲状腺-副腎-
it's a membrane that is both like this
性腺軸は、このように
but which expands a bit like this downwards with the pituitary gland
なっている膜ですが、下垂体とともに下の方に少し広がっています。
we see the third ventricle
第三脳室が見えます。
and we see the sphenoid, and we see this
そして蝶形骨が見え、この
membrane here.
膜がここに見えます。
Third ventricle, membrane of the illiquist that sets in here.
第三脳室、ここに位置する液体の膜。
All this cranial movement will actually be quite important and
この頭蓋の動き全体は、実際には非常に重要であり、
interesting to revisit
再検討する価値があります。
when you take a skull, to see a little bit of these different
頭蓋骨を取るとき、これらの異なる
movements at the level of your parietals.
頭頂骨の動きを少し見てください。
At the level of things, because in fact, they will follow certain lines of force, you
物事のレベルで、なぜなら実際には、それらは特定の力の線に従うからです、ほら。
see.
ほら。
And when I have this flexion movement at the frontal level, with the metopic suture,
そして、前頭縫合を伴う前頭部の屈曲運動があるとき、
these two balance points and these movements, it will have an influence on the movement of the eye.
これら2つのバランスポイントとこれらの動きは、眼の動きに影響を与えます。
So we will first do a first work, which is to know that the brain will condition the ventricular system
したがって、まず最初に行うべきことは、脳がその組織において
in its organization and will condition...
脳室系を条件付け、そして条件付けることを知ることです。
facial system. So the face and the skull. As well
顔面システム。つまり、顔と頭蓋骨です。
on the plan of the chondrocranium as
軟骨頭蓋と
of the desmocranium. Desmocranium is the membrane. Chondrocranium,
膜性頭蓋の両方で。膜性頭蓋は膜です。軟骨頭蓋は
it's the cartilage. Viscerocranium
軟骨です。内臓頭蓋
and neurocranium. If you look at a skull,
と神経頭蓋。頭蓋骨を見ると、
when I take this development phase
この発達段階を考えると、
and I explained all this movement to you, at the moment when I have my oxygen,
そして、このすべての動きを説明すると、酸素があるとき、
Reciput that descends.
後頭骨が下がります。
I have my sacrum that descends.
仙骨が下がります。
And you see the point, here, my temporals over there.
そして、ここ、私の側頭骨がそこにあるのがわかります。
And here, when it does that, what is the resulting poetics?
そして、これがこうなると、結果として生じる詩は？
It's my sternum that rises.
胸骨が上がります。
Since everything converges towards the anterior median line,
なぜなら、すべてが前正中線に収束するからです。
whether from Ignon,
イグノンからであろうと、
Nasion, sorry, towards the maxilla, towards the whole
鼻、失礼、上顎骨へ、すべての
system, you see.
システムへ、わかりますか。
And all that is inscribed in the eye.
そして、これらすべては目に刻まれています。
I dive.
私は深く潜ります。
Do you understand?
わかりますか？
How?
どうやって？
We're going to add more elements to that.
さらに要素を追加します。
We're going to add the whole facial system, the whole capsular system of the eye
眼のすべての顔面システム、すべての被膜システムを追加します。
which inserts around and completely organizes all that
それは周囲に挿入され、逆回転によってすべてを完全に組織化します。
with counter-rotation.
逆回転によって。
at the level, here,
ここ、
of development
発達の
orbit.
眼窩の。
So, these are two movements
したがって、これらは2つの動きであり、
that go in two different directions.
2つの異なる方向に向かいます。
This is the development
これは、
cranio-sterno-sacral
頭蓋-胸骨-仙骨
and mandibular.
および下顎の発達です。
And the canine axes.
そして犬歯の軸。
I see that on the face.
私はそれを顔に見ます。
I see your electric field
私はあなたの電場を
on your face.
あなたの顔に見ます。
By dint of looking.
見続けると、
You'll see that.
それがわかるでしょう。
We see, tac, tac.
私たちは、カチッ、カチッと見ます。
With sometimes
時には
certain lines that will appear.
現れる特定の線。
The line of worries.
心配の線。
The line of anger.
怒りの線。
And there, you understand
そして、ここで理解できるのは、
how the membrane of the illiquist
ヘリキストの膜が
is also in there.
その中にもあるということ。
And that it rebalances.
そして、それが再均衡化するということ。
And that all the vascularization,
そして、すべての血管新生、
all the optimization
すべての最適化、
trophic
栄養的なものが
is dependent on oxytocin.
オキシトシンに依存しているということ。
all that, how we can have a gradual loss.
これらすべてが、どのようにして徐々に失われていくのか。
And tomorrow, we'll go further into volemia again.
そして明日、私たちはさらに血液量について深く掘り下げていきます。
And then, we'll go into the movements.
そして、動きについても見ていきます。
Why?
なぜか？
When you go looking for an image
画像を探すとき、
or something specific,
または特定の何か、
creative or a memory or things like that,
創造的なもの、記憶、あるいはそのようなものを見るとき、
how will your eyes lengthen to look?
どのように目が伸びていくのか？
If you look at the eyes, we already see,
目を見ると、すでにわかります。
you see here, I have one eye that is more sunken over there.
ここを見てください、私の片方の目はもっと奥に引っ込んでいます。
I have one eye that looks like this.
私の片方の目はこのように見ています。
I have one eye that does this.
私の片方の目はこのように動いています。
So it's in two different spaces.
つまり、それは2つの異なる空間にあります。
But that's how it has its fulcrum.
しかし、それがその支点なのです。
If you don't have the upper and lower canine meeting,
もし上顎と下顎の犬歯が接触しない場合、
you have a loss of information at the brain level.
脳レベルでの情報が失われます。
Why?
なぜか？
Because these are electric fields that must unite.
なぜなら、それは結合すべき電場だからです。
If I don't have the contact made correctly,
もし接触が正しく行われない場合、
I lose my contact.
私は接触を失います。
occlusion and so what do I do I will change I will work my
咬合、そして私は何をしますか？私は自分の歯をできる限り変え、制約を変えるために働きます。なぜなら、歯は
teeth as best I can to change my constraints because the teeth
歯は制約を受け入れ、私の衝撃を回復させるためです。だからこそ、
they
咬合は、あなたの蝶形骨基底結合に見られる張力のタイプを反映しています。歯を観察すれば、歪みがあるかどうかがわかります。
take constraints to find my impact at the level that's why
もしあなたが
that
歪みがあるかどうかを知ることができます。
occlusion is the reflection of the type of tension found on your sphenobasilar
蝶形骨基底結合に見られる張力のタイプを反映しています。歯を観察すれば、歪みがあるかどうかがわかります。
symphysis you observe the teeth and you can tell if you have a strain
もしあなたが
have rotation side bending or you see
回旋側屈とか、わかるかな
etc. Vertical strain up, vertical strain down
など。垂直歪み上、垂直歪み下
or also lateral strain.
あるいは横方向の歪みも。